As a tower,
the studio is too conspicuous
and easily discovered by others.
So,
this place
is the real tower.
Because of Allen,
this case couldn't be closed as an accident.
You haven't had time to clean up these places.
On the bedsheets,
we can definitely find your and Mu Weijie's DNA.
If you still deny it,
we can run trace evidence analysis.
You really are a cop.
Very impressive.
Makes sense.
Whatever happens,
always leaves a trace.
The day Rongrong got hurt,
I actually knew
she had gone through the same thing as me.
That night,
she suddenly asked me to keep her company at her place.
And her expression,
her demeanor,
I was all too familiar with them.
Because I had already
experienced all of this myself.
I will never forget that day.
It was raining.
I was soaked.
He offered to drive me.
In the end.
I fell asleep.
We're here.
Mr. Mu, this doesn't seem to be where my house is.
Did we go the wrong way?
Mr. Mu, if there's nothing else, I'll be going.
Thank you, sir.
Come back.
Xiaoyue.
Mr. Mu, you can't do this.
Mr. Mu.
Don't hide.
Help! Help!
Help!
Be good, Xiaoyue.
You can't escape.
Xiaoyue.
Be more obedient next time.
Look.
So violent.
You even broke this.
This doesn't seem to be the direction to your house.
Xiaoyue.
I advise you not to call the police.
I guarantee your reputation will be ruined.
You'd better think about your mother.
Think about your mom.
Since that day,
every day has been a nightmare.
And I have to pretend nothing's wrong at home.
I'm afraid my mom will notice something's wrong
and worry about me.
What about your boyfriend, Alan?
Wasn't he with you?
Of course I wanted him to be with me.
But when I was in the most pain,
he couldn't give me any comfort.
Excuse me.
I need to take this.
Hello, Qiaoyue.
What are you doing?
Just tell me what you want.
I'm busy right now.
Where are you right now?
Where else could I be?
A friend just introduced me to a client.
We're discussing business.
I miss you.
Okay, okay.
I'll go see you when I'm done, alright?
I can't just leave my client here.
But I want to see you right now.
I've had enough of this.
You do this every time.
I'm working.
I'm not fooling around.
We're discussing a big project.
If it goes well, we'll have money to buy a house.
Okay?
Can you just trust me a little?
Who is it?
Hello, ma'am.
Who are you?
I am
an instructor at Qiaoyue Art Studio.
My last name is Mu.
Mr. Mu,
I've heard a lot about you.
Come, come.
Please have a seat.
I bought some fruit for you.
I'll put it on the coffee table.
Xiaoyue,
look who's here.
Ma'am, it's fine.
I'll go find her.
Okay.
Xiaoyue, come out.
Mr. Mu has been here for a while.
You should come greet him.
Ma'am, she's out.
Mom, sit.
Let Mr. Mu sit down.
Qiaoyue,
I came today
just to see how you're doing.
You haven't seemed yourself in class lately.
I'm doing very well.
Thank you, Mr. Mu.
Oh, really?
Let Mr. Mu sit down.
Let him sit down.
Ma'am, I'll seat myself.
Xiaoyue,
pour Mr. Mu a glass of water.
What's wrong?
My hand slipped.
Feed me.
What happened?
My hand slipped.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
I spilled some water on the floor myself.
Please don't mind her, Mr. Mu.
This child grew up without a father.
And I'm blind.
I didn't raise her well.
Ma'am, please don't say that.
I think you raised her very well.
She's a wonderful child.
Is she?
She
has a real talent for painting.
I came here this time
mainly to tell you something.
I specially selected some of Xiaoyue's best works
to exhibit at an art exhibition.
I... I am blind.
I can't see.
It's fine, ma'am.